Hey everyone and welcome to a new video. Today I'm going to show you a lot of pants, fake leather pants from Cheshkulfit.
And I'm going to give you an overview of their product range because they have cool push-up booty effect pants and tops.
And I think I'll show you the basic black one first.
This is like the basic one I would recommend to everyone, four leather pants.
and I think you might call this shapewear because there is this push-up booty effect
also with the tops I'm going to show you later on and you have fake pockets you can't put your
hands in there I'm always confused by that but it looks better without the pockets being here
it's basically mid-raise so not too high and it's very comfortable in the inside you have a
rubber band so the pants don't slide down which is really thoughtful and cool
I wanted to show them to you like this first but now I'm going to complete a
look and put on some boots and a jacket for the full leather optic I just added
the boots some over my knee ones and now the jacket
Let me check.
Yeah, this is kind of cool.
It's not your normal everyday look probably, but let's be honest, my channel is not for everyday looks.
Definitely going to wear that one out.
I think it has a nice kind of biker style, which I really like.
Of course, you'll find all the links in the description text.
I'm going to show you the leggings today, but also shaper tops, short jumpsuits and long jumpsuits.
and a bunch of different colors. You'll be surprised. So let's change into the next outfit.
Did you expect that? Probably not. It's pink. It's like a pearl sheen pink. I really
think it's a beautiful color, like the inside of a shell. That's what this color reminds me of.
And this is the matching top to the pants. They call it Shaper. I just simply say top.
The cool thing is that it fits really good, it's really tight, the cups are padded so you don't need a bra.
And it just matches the pants perfectly basically.
It's a really cool look also together.
I don't think it's too much because of the pastel quality of the color.
And I know, it's a running gag. I don't like pink. I still don't like pink.
but with blue hair pink looks really good on me so I keep ordering pink stuff and it still looks
good on me that's why there's another pink piece in this video and it probably won't stop
not that I'm going to wear it for work or something like that I'll stick to black
in my daily life but I mean for pictures it's really fun
This is actually the same pants as the black one and I'm wearing size medium in both items.
So as every time check the sizing charts.
SlashGelid does not only have the pants in the top spot, they also combined it and made
a catsuit or jumpsuit out of it in short and long and I'm going to show you the first version
in short. What do you think of the short catsuit? I like this color because it's a cool alternative
to black. If you want to have a splash of color and be a bit more subtle than such a bright in
your face color so this is a recommendation color wise. I think the fit is also really cool. It's
long enough in the body. I have a feeling that it runs slightly bigger than the pants and top
and I mean you could also add some high boots here or a fun tights if you want to do like a
more dressed look or add another leather jacket. I think it's a really cool basic to combine
also with all the zippers which are decoration. The only one you can open is the one in the front.
Another two-piece combination. This time the black shaper top which I think is a really really cool basic and I will use super often. And a pants in biker optic and style because of all the zippers and this ruffle part here.
I was a bit confused first when I put on the pants because I was like where's the second zipper and then I realized that it's asymmetrical and I think it is a nice design feature also with the zippers here too of this side and only one here so it's not too similar and you have something to look at also the zipper here in the back
and I paired it with some normal shoes because the pants need a lot of attention with all that
that's going on I don't know if you could already tell it but compared to the first pants this is a
different fabric it's a bit shinier so this is the shiny fall leather and this is the matte fall
leather that's why I paired the top to the biker leggings because it's the same fabric
Shashkely does not only have four leather fabrics but also normal fabrics. I'm going to show you
like the everyday jeans next. I paired it with the matching top. I don't know if it is a bit too much
or not with the gray. It's a completely different look than the fake leather ones. I'm going to tell
you why I love gray jeans compared to black jeans. If you wash black jeans too much they
eventually turn gray and are not a dark black anymore and look weird but it
doesn't happen with gray so you're on the safe side here these are actually
high-rise so I end here in my what's it called my waist in my waist above my
belly button something like that and what I definitely love about all the
pants they're really long so I can wear them with pumps and it doesn't look weird because it doesn't
show my ankles I don't like that so really big plus point for shashkill feels and they're also
super comfortable again even more comfortable than the fake leather ones because this fabric
is really really stretchy you can check out the homepage I link down below because you have
different options like the rise or with a zipper with buttons and different styles overall and I'm
going to switch into the catsuit for the last outfit I don't know what to say no I'm kidding
I have plenty to say I want to tell you a bit about the fabric because it's really firm fabric
which is cool for this kind of fake leather stuff and it's also because it's so firm shaping the
body a bit and it's really comfy everything I've worn was so comfy and made me look so good and
made my body look really cool but from the sizing I have to say again that the catsuits I would size
down next time and wear size s for the catsuits I mean it fits but could be a bit tighter
and I think it's a really cool look if you like want to wear a catsuit but do not want to look
too fetishy because it is like a really cool fashion look so summary of the sizing I'm 173
centimeters tall normally wear size 34 or 36 in the pants today I've worn size medium for the tops
and the pants and they did fit perfectly for catsuits I would recommend for myself a size S
next time okay I hope you enjoyed this video I had a lot of fun trying on all these outfits
check out the Sashkülfüth homepage I'll link everything down below and leave a comment and
tell me which one was your favorite I'm going to see you in the next video have a nice day bye